[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Dirty Dancing, Lisa says there is a pretty view from where?", "correct_answer": "The 1st Tee", "incorrect_answers": ["The 2nd Tee", "The 3rd Tee", "The 9th Tee"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was the film Bambi released?", "correct_answer": "1942", "incorrect_answers": ["1946", "1933", "1936"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Say Anything, what kind of car does Lloyd drive?", "correct_answer": "Blue Chevy Malibu", "incorrect_answers": ["Green pick-up truck", "Brown Trans Am", "Red Chevette"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Bronsted-Lowry acid-base classification, an acid is defined as a proton donor and a base is a proton acceptor.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long does a panda usually live in captivity?", "correct_answer": "20 - 30 years", "incorrect_answers": ["10 - 15 years", "80 - 90 years", "55 - 65 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The smallest cell in the human body is the ovum.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed and starred in the 1941 drama film Citizen Kane?", "correct_answer": "Orson Welles", "incorrect_answers": ["Herbert Wells", "Omar Sharif", "Anthony Quinn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of cigarettes does Kevin give Billy in St. Elmos Fire, when he boards the bus to leave D.C?", "correct_answer": "Newport", "incorrect_answers": ["Marlboro", "Camel", "Salem"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What color was the tape on the arrow that Leroy caught in The Last Dragon?", "correct_answer": "blue", "incorrect_answers": ["red", "yellow", "green"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the wall created by Gregs father to celebrate his achievements in the 2004 movie Meet the Fockers?", "correct_answer": "Wall of Gaylord", "incorrect_answers": ["Wall of Bravery", "Wall of Life", "Wall of Fame"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pi Day is celebrated by many lovers of the mathematical constant, \u03c0, on what date?", "correct_answer": "March 14th", "incorrect_answers": ["May 5th", "January 13th", "December 3rd"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This undergarment was originally introduced in 1968 by Gossard, with the byline \u201cmakes 34 look 36, makes 36 look pow\u2026\u201d.", "correct_answer": "Wonderbra", "incorrect_answers": ["Lingerie", "Briefs", "Camisole"]}]